coolseller.co.uk 2012-11-20

# CoolSeller Business Directory - Privacy Policy

**CoolSeller Privacy Policy  
**

CoolSeller Business Directory respects our visitor’s right to the privacy of their personal information they provide us on the CoolSeller.co.uk. This shows our dedication and commitment for high quality services we provide to our customers. The Following policy is intended to explain how your personal information will be treated as you make use of our services. We will not pass your information to any third party.

**1). Type of information we collect and how we use it**

We collect personal information and may be business information when you register or submit your business to CoolSeller Business Directory. Personal information includes your name, e-Mail address, personal URL or any other personal info you provide. 

We only show your business information and part of your personal information when visitors search businesses which are similar to yours. It helps to highlight your business and easy for the visitors to reach to you, if they want your services.

**2). View or edit personal information**

Users can view or edit their information when ever they want. If they want their personal information to be removed from CoolSeller they can use contact us form to forward their request for removal.

**3). Disclosure of personal information**

CoolSeller Business Directory will not otherwise use or disclose your personal information without your consent except as requested by government or law enforcement authorities.

**4). Traffic Statistics  
**Like most of the web, we may keep track record of CoolSeller visitors through third party web traffic analysers. That data is only used for analysis of visitor behaviour on CoolSeller to improve our service quality.

**5). CoolSeller Contents  
**CoolSeller contains many links to other sites on the web. We cannot control and are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other Web sites.

If you have any further questions or concerns about our privacy policies please don’t hesitate to contact us.

**We may update this policy periodically, so please check back from time to time.**
